Google Dhan ₹2 please like, share and
subscribe and Nifty Bank Mahal has gone up by 120 points,
so is this the level
where there is another opportunity for new buying?
I am Lakshmi Rasta. We should also wait from Megha.
Anyway, if you look at Dubai, it is a
time to call an unwanted guest, so let's
wait a little and
16 223 is the tax on which I will probably
think once that we should not do it for picking the log, let's
wait a little, Massa and staff commission,
see the maths, taking the full advantage off,
Reliance thing, apart from this, HDFC
Bank, which used to travel above 1000 in the morning, was in this,
apart from this, Maharashtra is apprehensive that
I welcome you, I was asking what is
happening at the
place of Bigg Boss, but keep in mind that
Mitti did its 0995 now, which
was around Dahej and it was around Reddy Bank
and profit booking was seen there,
so I have booked this book, you have to buy at current levels,
wait a little, there will be
clarity, only then you can buy in Nifty.
If it dips below 16250,
then another thing is that after that you will
see a correction, you will get about 150
points and you will see 16161, so keep in mind the
level of 16250, if
you are ahead below it, then you
can start from the stalls of 16335,
take 16108, but before that there is no
train to Bihar, it is better to wait and you will
buy only when there will be 10 backs, the
soil will come out above it, then you have to
wait for 16425 435, it is
up to you to play the playlist, if it happens like this, will you
buy, it is an artisan matter, my
question is that ISI CIA, keep in
mind that it seems indicative here, there was
a very strong support, it will go from around 1240,
it has been done in between, the prices are
running at 1225, you can sell now,
apply 1240 catchup